complaint_text,priority,clean_text,clean_text_lemma,ner
My internet is not working for two days,High,My internet is not working for two days,"['internet', 'work', 'two', 'day']",[]
Billing error in my last invoice,Medium,Billing error in my last invoice,"['Billing', 'error', 'last', 'invoice']",[]
Website login page is very slow,Low,Website login page is very slow,"['Website', 'login', 'page', 'slow']","[('Website', 'GPE')]"
"Received wrong product, need urgent replacement",High,Received wrong product need urgent replacement,"['Received', 'wrong', 'product', 'need', 'urgent', 'replacement']",[]
Customer support is not responding,Medium,Customer support is not responding,"['Customer', 'support', 'respond']","[('Customer', 'GPE')]"
I am unable to access my Gmail account,High,I am unable to access my Gmail account,"['unable', 'access', 'Gmail', 'account']",[]
Met with John Doe yesterday regarding service issues,Medium,Met with John Doe yesterday regarding service issues,"['Met', 'John', 'Doe', 'yesterday', 'regard', 'service', 'issue']","[('Met', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('John Doe', 'PERSON')]"
Order from Amazon has not been delivered,High,Order from Amazon has not been delivered,"['Order', 'Amazon', 'deliver']","[('Order', 'GPE'), ('Amazon', 'GPE')]"
Flight to New York got cancelled without any notification,High,Flight to New York got cancelled without any notification,"['Flight', 'New', 'York', 'get', 'cancel', 'without', 'notification']","[('Flight', 'GPE'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
Warranty for my iPhone is still pending after two months,Low,Warranty for my iPhone is still pending after two months,"['Warranty', 'iPhone', 'still', 'pending', 'two', 'month']","[('Warranty', 'GPE'), ('iPhone', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Barack Obama was born in Hawaii and worked at Google.,,Barack Obama was born in Hawaii and worked at Google,"['Barack', 'Obama', 'bear', 'Hawaii', 'work', 'Google']","[('Barack', 'PERSON'), ('Obama', 'PERSON'), ('Hawaii', 'GPE'), ('Google', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
